Trevor Jex

Software Engineer

5568 W 10080 N Highland, UT 84003

385-286-7361 jextrevor@gmail.com https://portfolio.trevorjex.com

Skills

Extensive programming experience in Javascript, Python, C++, HTML, and CSS, with limited experience in C, C#, Golang, PHP, and SQL. Familiar with AWS, React, Node, and websockets. Significant experience with Linux and Git. List of projects available at https://portfolio.trevorjex.com.

Experience



BYU Broadcasting / Software Developer

JUNE 2018 - MAY 2019, PROVO UT

Software developer working on apps, websites, and services for BYUtv and BYU Radio as part of an agile team. Played a major part in transitioning BYUtv to an improved video encoding platform.



Omadi, Inc / Software Engineering Intern

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT, LEHI UT

Software engineer working on websites and services to facilitate fast and accurate towing management. Helping to transition away from PHP Drupal and towards newer technologies.

Education

Brigham Young University

SEPTEMBER 2018 - PRESENT, PROVO UT Majoring in Computer Science, 4.0 GPA.

American Fork High School

AUGUST 2015 - MAY 2018, AMERICAN FORK UT

Top 5% of graduating class, cumulative 4.0 GPA and 5 AP classes, section leader in Chamber Choir and Chamber Orchestra, 2018 Department Choice for Performing Arts, President of Latin Club 2017-18, Treasurer of Inter-Club Council 2017-18, Intel Excellence in Computer Science Award.

References

Cameron Sanchez / BYU Broadcasting Supervisor

801-427-5058 csanchez2237@gmail.com

Chris Crump / LDS Youth Leader

801-369-7092 chriscrump44@yahoo.com

Laurel Shelley / Latin Teacher

801-372-0551 ltshelley@gmail.com